Nate Gamble

31 Townsend Ct. Roseville, California, 95678 (719) 465 – 7994

Email: nate.eli.gamble@gmail.com
LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/nathan-gamble
Github: https://github.com/NateGamble

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Student who is ready and willing to contribute to an internship. Some experience in programming with C++, Python, Java, Ada, Lisp, Ruby, C# and Fortran and helping customers with their problems. Lots of experience in relating to people from across cultures.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science, Computer Science

Calvin College – Grand Rapids, Michigan GPA: 3.497

Relevant coursework:

- Data Structures and Algorithms
- Software Engineering
- Intro to Computer Architecture
- Advanced Chinese

- Discrete Mathematics
- Programming Language Concepts

May 2020 Expected

• System Administration

WORK EXPERIENCE

Knollcrest Dining Team Member

Calvin College – Grand Rapids, Michigan

• Help prepare and serve food to customers

Sep 2018 to Current

Lab Monitor

Calvin College – Grand Rapids, Michigan

- Help students with their problems writing code
- Fix bugs and found errors in code

Nov 2016 to Current

Crew Member

McDonald's - Roseville, California

- Prepared food in a high-pressure environment
- Maintained a clean environment at all times
- Cleaned heavy machinery

May 2017 to Aug 2017

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Biked 150 miles to raise money for the National Multiple Sclerosis Society
- Participated in a missions trip to Mozambique
- Participated in a trip to China to help high school students improve their English
- Lived cross culturally for almost 7 years in Uganda and India
- Volunteered at multiple triathlons
- Volunteered at a food closet

PROJECTS

- KnightRides Carpooling app
- Backgammon game GUI and very basic AI using randomness
- Mancala AI using minimax and alpha-beta pruning